Ada Peirce McCormick papers, 1881-1978 (bulk 1920-1974)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: General Files, ca. 1915-1978
  - Cardon, Charlotte (Mrs. Bartley). 1946-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Care. 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Carey, Graham. 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Carlson, Dr. Earl R. 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Carman, Reverend Charles. 1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Carpenter, Dr. Edwin and Ethel. 1960-1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Carpenter, Leonard and Winifred. 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Carroll, Dr. John F. 1963 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Carter, Russell Gordon. 1946-1952 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Cartesian Research Bureau (Marion E. Robinson). 1946 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Casey, Bera, (Mrs. Roy). 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Casmir, Fred. 1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Castiglioni, Dr. Arturo. 1944-1951 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Castro, Raul. 1963 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Catholic Worker. 1941-1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - The Catholic World. 1923-1950 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cenacle Convent and Retreat Mount Kisco, New York. 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Cerf, Bennett A. 1946 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Chafin, Eugene Wilder. 1960, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Boulder, Colorado. 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Chambers of Commerce. 1946-1951 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Chamberlin, Enola. 1951 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Chapel of Four Chaplains. 1951-1954 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Chapin, Adelaide. 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cheney, Rowena. 1948-1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Cheruy, Madame Cermaine. 1947-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - China 1942 (correspondence with Chinese Consuls). 1942-1948 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Exclusion Repeal. 1943 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Flyers. 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Student, scholarship. 1959 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Christian Century Press. 1946-1951 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Christian News-Letter. 1941-1945 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Christian Science Monitor. 1942-1956 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Christianity and Crisis. 1942-1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Christopher City Housing Development (Tucson). 1962-1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Christophers, Father James Keller. 1950-1961 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Church, Wade. 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Churchill, Winston. 1942 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Cigarette Advertising. 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Citizens League Against the Sonic Boom. 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Civilian Defense. 1942 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Claremont School of Theology. 1959-1972 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Clark, Mary Esther Treat. 1952-1974 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Clarke, John Henrik. 1946-1950 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Clawson, Mr. and Mrs. George H. 1951 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Clegg, Helen. 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cleghorn, Sarah. 1928-1951 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Clipping Bureaus. 1942-1944 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cohn, Edwin J. and Rebecca. 1952-1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cole, Reverend Wilson G. 1945-1947 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Collier, Zena. 1953 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Collier's Magazine. 1945-1952 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Commentary. 1949-1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Comics. 1949 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Committee to Defend America. 1941-1956 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America. 1943-1947 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America, Osborne and Orozco manuscripts. 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Common Cause, Inc. 1948-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Common Cause. 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Common Council for American Unity. 1941-1946 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Common Ground Magazine. 1940-1949 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Commonweal Magazine. 1944-1954 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Common Sense Magazine. 1942-1946 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Communism. 1946-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Compass. 1944-1947 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Conference on Intellectual Freedom. 1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Congdon, Elizabeth and Clara. 1932-1937 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Congdon, Mr. and Mrs. Edward; Robert. 1933-1966 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Congdon, Stephen and Persis. 1952-1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Congregational Church. 1959-1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Congress of Racial Equality. 1958-1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Conly, Robert. 1944 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Conner, Mary Effin. 1950 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Conroy, Tom. 1954 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Convent of Saint Anne. 1940-1954 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Convent of the Holy Nativity. 1942-1962 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Converse, James. 1945-1950 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Coolidge, Gloria (nurse for Schweitzer in Africa). 1935-1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Coolidge, Mrs. John T. 1948-1953 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Copeland, C.T. 1915 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Cosmopolitan Club. 1942-1973 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Cosulich, Bernice. 1948-1954 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Council Against Intolerance in America. 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Council for Democracy. 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Country Life Conference. 1947-1956 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Counts, George. 1952 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Coury, Reverend Moses G. 1943-1946 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Craftsmanship Magazine. 1948 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Craig, John. 1943-1950 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Craig, Mildred R.. 1943 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Crime Conference. 1949 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Cromwell, Fred. 1952-1955 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Crowell, Shirley. 1950-1967 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Crowther, Bishop Edward. 1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Culbertson, Ely. 1944-1946 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Culver, Monty. 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Culver, Monty. 1951-1955 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Cummings, Dr. Byron. ca. 1953 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Cunningham, Helen Zeta. 1943-1948 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Current Biography Magazine. 1945-1959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Curtis Publishing Company. 1943 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - D: Miscellaneous. 1925-1961 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Dagadu, Reverend Peter (Ghana). 1954-1958 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Daily Reporter. 1950 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dall, Marcus H. 1945 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Dalton, Dorothy. 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Dalton, Henry. 1950 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Damm, Alice. 1947-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Dandelet, Lucille. 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Danforth, William H. 1944-1952 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - d'Autremont, Chester, Hughes and Charles. 1940-1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - d'Autremont, Helen. 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - d'Autremont, Helen. 1940-1949 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - d'Autremont, Helen. 1950-1959 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - d'Autremont, Helen. 1960-1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - d'Autremont, Hubert. 1931-1947 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - d'Autremont Memorial Committee. 1966-1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Davis, A. F. 1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Davis, H. Clyde and Annabelle. 1957-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Eileen (Willen). 1950 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Elmer. 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Day, Dorothy. 1941-1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Day, Irene F. 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Day (John) Company. 1942-1954 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dayton, Paul K. and Nan. 1947-1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - De Angulo, Ximena. 1945-1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Deaton, Paul V. 1950-1952 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - De Grazia, Alexandra Diamos. 1945-1972 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - De Grazia, Ted. 1945-1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - De La Bedoyere, Michael. 1948-1961 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Delaney, Ed. 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Delaney, Sadie Peterson. 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Derby, Ethel Roosevelt. 1922-1938 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Derby, Ethel Roosevelt. 1940-1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Derby children. ca. 1920-1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - DeJong, David C. 1946-1949 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - De Ligorio, D.Alphonsi. No date (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - de Selincourt, Hugh. 1927-1948 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Diamos, George and David. 1945-1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dirks, J. Edward. 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Dixon, Dr. George and Ellen. 1945-1963 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Dodd, Mead and Co. 1943-1945 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Dodge, Hartley. 1947 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Dodge, Virginia Lee. 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Don, Luell (goddaughter of APM). 1946-1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Donaldson, Norman. 1953 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Dondero, George Anthony. 1952 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Dotis, Marilyn McNamara. 1949-1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Doubleday and Co. 1944-1951 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Doughty, Corporal S. Lewis. 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Douglas, Lewis and family. 1951-1968 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Douglas, Mary Peace (Mrs. James S.). 1949-1972 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Douglas, Walter and Annabelle. 1948-1969 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Douglass, Andrew Ellicott and Ida. 1935, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Dowdell, Reverend Charles and Frances. 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Drachman, Harry Cowan. 1943 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Dragonette, Fred and Jessica. 1940-1948 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Dravo, Hudson and Margaret. 1919-1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Dreier, Mary E. 1943-1946 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - D'Souza, Father Jerome. 1957-1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Dublin Conference. 1946 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Dubois, W.E.B. 1924, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Dudley, Harry and Marjorie. 1942-1966 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Duell, Sloan and Pearce. 1944-1952 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - du Nouy, Mary Lecomte. 1961 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Durham, Frank. 1952-1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Dutton, E.P. And Co. 1946-1954 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - E: Miscellaneous. 1939-1961 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - East and West Association. 1942-1948 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Eastman, Donald. 1955 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Eastman Kodak Co. 1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Eaton, Howard 0. 1948 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Ebony Magazine. 1945-1957 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Ecumenical Press. 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Edgerly, Beatrice. 1954 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Editor and Publisher. 1942-1961 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Editorial Research Report. 1950-1963 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Edmonson, Alvina (APM secretary). 1935, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Edmonson, Mr. and Mrs. E.S. 1952 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Ehrich, Louis and Florence. 1950-1962 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Einstein Foundation. 1946 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Ellinwood, Clare (Mrs. Ralph). 1943-1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Eiseley, Dr. Loren. 1962-1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Elkin, Sam. 1945-1948 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Elliston, Herbert. 1946-1950 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Elliston, Joey (Mrs. Herbert). 1942-1958 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Emancipator Magazine. 1943-1951 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Embassies (various countries). 1943, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Emperor of Japan, (cf Box 35/24). 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Entz, Mrs. John. 1943-1945 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Episcopal Church. 1941-1957 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Erasmus Magazine. 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Erdman, Dr. Charles. 1947-1956 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Evanhoe, Mrs. B.M. 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Evans, Mrs. Eva J. 1947 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Evans, Mrs. Evelyn E. 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Exiled Writers Committee. 1940-1941 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Exposition Press. 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - F: Miscellaneous. 1924-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Fair Employment Practices Commission. 1950-1953 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Fallout Suits (David Walden). 1958-1964 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Families for International Friendship. 1960 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Fannin, Paul. 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Farley, James. 1943-1946 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Farmer, Fyke (World Control of Atomic Energy). 1946-1948 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Feather, The William Magazine. 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Federal Prison Camp. 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Federal Union. 1940-1947 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Feierabend, Helga. 1952 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Feierabend, Helga. 1953 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Feierabend, Helga. 1954 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Feierabend, Helga. 1955 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation. 1925-1961 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship of Saint Alban and Saint Sergius. 1938-1968 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Fenn, Reverend Dan Huntington and Anna. 1951-1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Ferguson, Evelyn B. 1943-1950 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Ferguson, Reverend George and May. 1942-1968 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Ferry, Sarah and Alan. 1944-1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Field, Marshall, Jr. 1942-1948 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Findley, Earl N. 1943 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Fink, Arthur B. 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Finland, re: U.S. to lend money to Finland. 1940 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Finley, Mrs. John, re: Ida Tarbell. 1942-1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Fire. 1948, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fischer, Louis. 1945-1947 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fishbackil Jessamine. 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield. 1928-1929 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield. 1942-1945 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield. 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield. 1948-1958 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, manuscript. 1916 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Fitch, Geraldine (Mrs. George, supporter of Chiang-Kai-Shek and Korea). 1943-1957 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Fitzgerald, Ruth B. 1951-1954 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Flaherty (Robert) Foundation and Film Seminar. 1959-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Flandrau, Grace. 1947-1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Flynn, Clarence Edwin. 1949-1951 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Flynn, John T. 1952-1954 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Foerster, Frederick W. 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Folsom Observer. 1944 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Forbes, Dr. Robert H. 1953 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Fort Grant Industrial School. 1945-1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Fort Huachuca. 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Fort Lowell Homemakers. 1945-1972 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Fortune Magazine. 1942-1961 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Foster Parents Plan for Spanish Children. 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Foster Parents Plan for War Childern. 1938-1954 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Foster Parents Plan for War Children, (Kostalas, George). 1949-1954 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Foster Parents Plan for War Children, (Sammut, Edward). 1944-1950 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Foster Parents Plan for War Children, (Weissman, Wood, Frost). 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Foundation for Religious Action in the Social and Civil Order. 1954-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Foundations. 1955-1961 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Fowlie, Wallace. 1952 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Franklin, Anna S. 1950 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Franklin, Jessie Merle. 1949 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Free World Magazine. 1942-1946 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Freeman, G. William. 1945 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Freeman Magazine. 1952 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Fremantle, Anne. 1962 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Friedman, F. Louis. 1947-1952 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Friends of Arizona Libraries. 1948-1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Friends of the Land. 1948 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Frohmiller, Ana. 1949-1950 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Frontier Magazine. 1950-1961 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Frontier Nursing Sevvice. 1947, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fruehauf Trailer Company. 1942 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Fudge, Margaret Trimmell. 1950-1965 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Fumento, Rocco. 1950-1952 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Funk and Wagnalls Co. 1950-1952 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Furst, S. Dale. 1942-1969 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - G: Miscellaneous. 1931-1964 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Gaines, F. Pendleton and Dorothy. 1943, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Gallagher, Father V.R. 1954 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Gandhi, Nehru and Schweitzer. 1952 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Garden City Publishing Co. 1945 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Gardiner, Arthur. 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Gardner, Hilda M. 1943 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Gardner, Paul A. 1948-1952 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Gegenheimer, Albert and family. 1942-1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Geiger, Margaret. 1947-1951 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - General Semantics. 1949-1953 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Getts, Clark H. 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Getty, David J. 1953-1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Getty, Dr. Harry T. 1959-1967 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Getty, Jan. 1960-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Getty, Justine. 1948-1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Getty, Justine, re: trip to Yugoslavia. 1969 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1956 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1960 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1963 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie. 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie, (letters with J. Edgar Hoover). 1949-1951 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Gibbons, Marjorie, Intimations. No date (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Gift Replies. 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Gillis, Father James. 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Gillmor, Frances. 1944-1966 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Gilmore, Mrs. Thomas. 1949-1954 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Girard Case. 1957 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Glen, Emilie. 1949-1953 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Gless, Eleanor Green. 1945-1948 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Goddard, Sam and Judy. 1960-1966 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Goethe Bicentennial. 1949 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Goethe, C. M. 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Goldwater, Barry M. 1952-1961 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Goodhart, A.L. 1945-1967 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Gorer, Geoffrey. 1948-1954 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Gorman, Warren, M.D. 1965 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Gould, Mrs. S. Franklin. 1954-1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Gowen, Mary Ellen. 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Grace Episcopal Church. 1939-1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Graham, Clem. 1950-1951 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Graham, Shirley. 1943-1949 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Grail Review, (Lorraine Machan). 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Grant, Marie. 1952 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Graves, Anna Melissa. 1942-1949 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Graves, Anna M.(letters from Andree Etienne). 1944-1947 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Gray, Adeline. 1949-1951 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Green, Carolyn. 1946-1957 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Green, William. 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Greenberg Publisher. 1950-1952 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Green Fields School. 1944-1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Greene, Ernest and Carolyn. 1951-1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Greene, Henry Copley. 1943-1948 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Greene, H.P.S. 1945-1947 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Greenway, Jack. 1938-1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Grenzeback, Joe E. 1946-1953 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Grieve, Marion. 1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Griffin, John H., (Lew Smollett). 1951-1953 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Grit Publishing Co. 1943-1963 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni. 1951 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Gross, Edwin A. 1947-1953 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Guerrero, Joey. 1948-1959 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Guideposts Magazine re: article by APM. 1949-1972 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - H: Miscellaneous. 1923-1969 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Hadassah. 1948-1970 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Hagen, Mabel McNeill. 1946-1949 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Hamilton, Dr. Alice H. 1926-1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Hamilton, Marie. 1950-1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Co. 1943-1961 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Harijan. 1947-1949 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Harlem Book Co. 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Harlem Quarterly. 1950 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Harper, Margaret Pease. 1939-1970 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Harlan, Esther. 1944-1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Harmon, John Frank, Jr. 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Harper and Brothers. 1926-1962 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Harrington, C. Henry. 1943-1958 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Harlem, Rachel. 1944 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Harless, Richard. 1944-1954 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Harte, Bishop Joseph M. 1963-1965 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Harter, Helen O'Connor. 1943-1947 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Harvard Divinity School. 1952 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Harvard University. 1940-1961 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Harvill, Dr. Richard. 1951-1971 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Harvill, George (Mrs. Richard). 1955-1969 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Haskell, Carolyne Hyde. 1951-1969 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Haskell, Melville H. 1942-1951 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Hawkins, Anne Gray. 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Hayden, Carl. 1937-1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Headlines and Pictures. 1945-1946 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Hearn, John H. 1958 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Heckler, Willie J. 1949-1951 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Helfer, Harold. 1946-1955 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Helmericks, Connie. 1960-1968 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Hemingway, Ernest. 1964 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Henderson, Esther. No date (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Herring, Daniel Boone. 1945 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Herrick, George Fielden. 1948 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Hersey, Jean. 1947 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Hess, Naomi Reynolds. 1950-1951 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Hewlett, A.E. May. 1946-1951 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Hickok, Mrs. Helen. 1949 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Higbee, Alma Robison. 1950 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Higginson, Rebekah Robinson. 1937-1955 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Higley, Lutie. 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Hill, Mary. 1950 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Hilton Corporation. 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Hintz, Helen (Mrs. Howard). ca. 1967-1972 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Hirohito, Emperor of Japan, (cf. Box 25/8). 1954-1961 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Hill, Dr. Donald and Ruth. 1951-1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Hironimus, Helen. 1943-1961 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - History of Science Society. 1952-1956 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Hiwot, Abeba. 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Hobbs, Reverend William H. 1950-1962 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Hobo News. 1946 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Hocking, Hester. ca. 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Hodges, Leigh Mitchell. 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Hodson, Joy. 1958 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Hoffman, Dr. Frederick. 1947 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Hogan, Alice. 1949-1952 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Hollywood Quarterly. 1945 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Holmes, Dr. and Mrs. Fred. 1944-1947 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Holsclaw, Douglas. 1954-1960 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Holt, Henry and Co. 1946-1950 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Holy Trinity School, Haiti. 1959-1967 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Hopper, Franklin. 1946-1947 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Horvath, Felice de. 1951-1953 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Hospitals in Arizona. 1960-1965 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Houghton, Beatrice Y. 1952 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co. 1946-1954 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Houselander, Caryll. 1946-1954 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Houston, Mayor E. T. 1950 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Howard, Edwin. 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Howard, Lewis. 1950 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Howard, Maud. 1941-1955 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Hughes, Betty Upton. 1943 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Hughes, Dorothy B. 1949 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Hughes, Rupert. 1943 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Hughes, Sidney, Jr. 1943-1950 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Hughston, Mary. 1946-1970 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Humane Society of Tucson. 1952-1961 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Humanists. 1954 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Hummel, Don. 1957-1965 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Humphreys, Elizabeth. 1949 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Huot, Irene. 1950-1958 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Hutchens, Jane. 1948 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Hutchins, Maude. 1951-1956 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Hutchins, Robert. 1947-1952 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Hutchins, William J. 1944-1949 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Hutchins, William J. and Anna. 1950-1953 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Hutchinson, G. Evelyn. 1952 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hwang Sung San (US Army Air Force, Chinese detachment). 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - I: Miscellaneous. 1941-1968 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - India, APM advertisement. 1942 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - India, APM editorials. 1943 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - India, Haridas Mazumdar. 1942 (Box 37, Folder 8)